I came here this time
mainly to report something to you.
Oh.
I specifically selected some of Xiaoyue's best works
to display at the art exhibition.
I... I am blind.
I can't see.
It's fine, Auntie.
Even if you can't see,
we artists believe that
by feeling with your heart,
you can still appreciate the artwork.
This is the meaning of our artwork.
I'm begging you.
Right?
Why are there so many?
Why don't we let Xiaoyue take a look?
No need.
These are Xiaoyue's own works.
She has already seen them.
Xiaoyue, do you want to take another look?
Have a look.
All right.
Auntie, I'll let her take another look.
Xiaoyue.
Teacher.
These are the ones selected.
What do you think?
These are the ones I really like.
Xiaoyue,
are they really beautiful?
Tell Mom about them.
Of course they are.
Hurry up and tell Auntie.
They are very beautiful, Mom.
Then hurry up
and thank your teacher.
It's what I should do.
Auntie,
Qiaoyue is moved to tears.
Is that so?
It's all because you are a good teacher.
Xiaoyue,
you must thank your teacher properly.
I think for Xiaoyue,
if she continues studying like this,
she will definitely have a bright future.
Okay.
Thank you.
Auntie,
I'll be leaving now.
Okay.
Hey, Qiaoyue.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong before.
I miss you.
I'll go find you.
I don't want to see you right now.
Don't come over.
Qiaoyue.
What exactly happened to you?
Allen, let's break up.
I'm really tired.
Are you crazy?
Let's just leave it at that.
Qiaoyue.
Xiaoyue.
You're not asleep yet, are you?
Not yet.
What's wrong?
Let me tell you.
Xiaoyue.
Mr. Mu said
he wants to put your painting in the exhibition.
You've made something of yourself.
I am so happy.
I just don't know how to thank him.
I picked these fruits
with my own hands.
You should take them to him.
You are so outstanding.
I am really proud.
Honey.
Honey, it's really urgent.
Listen to me.
I really have something urgent to tell you.
Spit it out.
I'm in a hurry.
Go ahead.
I've run out of my creative funds.
But
I've finished my artwork.
It will definitely fetch a good price this time.
You know,
creation requires inspiration.
Inspiration needs to be found.
Finding inspiration means experiencing life,
which requires money, right?
Experiencing life?
Don't think I don't know
what you did with that money.
You can play with fire,
but don't go too far.
Be careful, your little heart might not be able to take it.
Don't worry.
I'll take my medicine on time.
All right.
I'll arrange for finance to wire you the money tomorrow.
Thank you, honey.
I'm in a hurry. I have to go.
There's no one else here.
Who are you showing off your affection to?
Mr. Mu.
Honey.
I'll leave you to your work.
I'm leaving now.
Be careful.
This is the fruit my mom asked me to bring you.
I...
I want to drop out of school.
Have I been treating you too well these past few days?
How dare you speak to me like that.
Do you also look down on me?
I'm telling you.
When my work is completed,
I'll make everyone who looks down on me regret it.
Wait for me.
I sympathize with your situation,
and I understand how you feel.
But I am a police officer.
The law shows no mercy.
If he broke the law,
the law will punish him.
He will definitely receive the punishment he deserves.
But you
chose to fight evil with evil.
Now look,
we can only arrest you.
Fight evil with evil.
Arrest me.
Officer Zhuang.
I didn't break any laws, did I?
Did I commit murder or arson?
Mu Weijie is the one who broke the law.
He committed rape,
date rape,
intimidation,
and false imprisonment.
He is the one you should be arresting.
Whether we arrest him or not
and how we do it is none of your business.
Right now, all you need to do is cooperate.
You've already closed this case, right?
Closed as an accident.
You caused all these accidents.
Because you knew
if you called the police,
Mu Weijie would fight back desperately.
But if you killed him yourself,
you would be punished by the law.
So,
you created all these accidents.
I pulled off an accident.
I'm so amazing.
Where is the evidence?
I don't think I'm that capable.
Of course you are.